{"data":[{"question":"The new workers aren't used for the working conditions here.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"aren't","b":"for","c":"working","d":"here","answer":"2","explain":"- For-> to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"It is a common saying that we do not full value a thing until we lose it.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"common","b":"full","c":"until","d":"lose","answer":"2","explain":"- Full-> fully","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Mary, which car broke down, had to take a taxi.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"which","b":"down","c":"had to","d":"a","answer":"1","explain":"- Which-> whose","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"When considering of equal value, the goods can be exchanged.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"When","b":"considering","c":"equal","d":"be","answer":"2","explain":"- Considering-> considered","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"She is no longer a beautiful girl any more.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"a","c":"beautiful","d":"any more","answer":"4","explain":"- Any more-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Mary is finally used to cook on electric stove.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"finally","c":"to cook","d":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- To cook-> cooking","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"It is not true that the British talks about the weather more than any other nation.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"talks","c":"more than","d":"any other","answer":"2","explain":"- Talks-> talk","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"When I heard the telephone ring, I will answer it immediately.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"When","b":"ring","c":"will answer","d":"immediately","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Will aswer-> answered","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"I study English so that to improve my knowledge.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"study","b":"so that","c":"to improve","d":"my knowledge","answer":"3","explain":"- So that-> so as","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"},{"question":"Jane was standing outside a shop when I was seeing her.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was standing","b":"outside","c":"when","d":"was seeing","answer":"4","explain":"- Was seeing-> saw","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"29","type":"1"}]}